<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HelloKotlin</string>

    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Chelsea FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
    </array>

    <array name="club_description">
        <item>Futbol Club Barcelona, known simply as Barcelona and colloquially as Barça, is a
            professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain
        </item>
        <item>Real Madrid Club de Fútbol, commonly known as Real Madrid, is a professional football
            club based in Madrid, Spain. Founded on 6 March 1902 as the Madrid Football Club, the
            club has traditionally worn a white home kit since inception
        </item>
        <item>Fußball-Club Bayern München e.V., commonly known as FC Bayern München, FCB, Bayern
            Munich, or FC Bayern, is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria
        </item>
        <item>Manchester City Football Club, commonly known as City, is a football club in
            Manchester, England. Founded in 1880 as St. Mark, it became Ardwick Association Football
            Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894
        </item>
        <item>Manchester United Football Club, commonly known as Man. United or simply United, is a
            professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England, that
            competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football
        </item>
        <item>Chelsea Football Club is a professional football club in London, England, that
            competes in the Premier League. Founded in 1905, the clubs home ground since then has
            been Stamford Bridge. Chelsea won the First Division title in 1955, followed by various
            cup competitions between 1965 and 1971
        </item>
        <item>Associazione Calcio Milan, commonly referred to as A.C. Milan or simply Milan, is a
            professional football club in Milan, Italy, founded in 1899. The club has spent its
            entire history, with the exception of the 1980–81 and 1982–83 seasons, in the top flight
            of Italian football, known as Serie A since 1929–30
        </item>
        <item>Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club based in Islington, London,
            England, that plays in the Premier League, the top flight of English football
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="league">
        <item>English Premier League</item>
        <item>English League Championship</item>
        <item>German Bundesliga</item>
        <item>Italian Serie A</item>
        <item>French Ligue 1</item>
        <item>Spanish La Liga</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="id_league">
        <item>4328</item>
        <item>4329</item>
        <item>4331</item>
        <item>4332</item>
        <item>4334</item>
        <item>4335</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_football_matchtab">FootballMatchtabActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_football_match_schedule">Football Match Schedule</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Last Match</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Next Match</string>
    <string name="football_match_schedule">Football Match Schedule</string>
    <string name="list_football_from_api">List of Football From API</string>
</resources>
